[{"answer": "Time is money, my friend. We need extra beer today", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Very good", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Forgive the hurry but I do not want you to miss the lunch buffet on the paddle steamer across the lake. It is the most spectacular sight in all Africa", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Exactly, we can't have our guests starving. What would they think of the that place back in the that place", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yes, it is a calamity for us all", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No. I work at the that place", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes. With some r", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yes we have", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "All. What do you mean all", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "The staff and guests! How many", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What do you want", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "The commander is not here", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "We are to meet Mr. my friend", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He will be here", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What cards", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Our cards, please", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You have our cards", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What was the bribe?  What am I worth to you", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "To be closer. So that I could marry you", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It was substantial", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What was the bribe?  What am I worth to you", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Tell me what it was", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Tell me what it was", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What sort of car", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I want to know", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "A that place", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "They will surely kill us here. It's over here. We have to take the chance", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "We'll be chopped here", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No, sir", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "I hope we all get to do many things. Can we go now", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "How so", "docId": "Hotel-Rwanda.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I am on a list! What list", "qsentId": 34}]